https://hebrewcollege.edu/privacy-policy/

Please click here to donate to Hebrew College by December 31 & help unlock an $18,000 match!
Become a Rabbi
CurriculumCommunityAlumni & Career PlacementAdmissions & Financial Aid
Become a Cantor
CurriculumCommunityAlumni & Career PlacementAdmissions & Costs
Become an Educational Leader
Graduate Education ProgramsAlumni & Career PlacementAdmissions
Community Education
Study Opportunities
Hebrew Language (Ulpan & Graduate Level)Interfaith LearningJewish History & ThoughtJewish TextsJewish LivingJudaism for TeensMindfulness & SpiritualityMusic20s & 30s
Adult Programs
Fall 2020 Community Education OpportunitiesHebrew Language (Ulpan & Graduate Level)Me'ah: Classic & SelectOpen Circle Jewish Learning & Social ActionOpen Circle 20s & 30s (Eser)Parenting & Grandparenting Through a Jewish LensMiller Center for Interreligious Learning & LeadershipRabbinical, Cantorial & Education Classes (non-credit)Community Education Faculty
Teen Learning
Prozdor: Where Jewish Teens ThriveJTFGB (Teen Philanthropy)Teen Beit MidrashKivunim (Gap-Year Program)
Professional Development
Hebrew College Innovation LabFor Educational LeadersMiller Center: Interreligious Engagement
Admissions
Apply NowGraduate Degrees & GuidelinesRabbinical OrdinationCantorial OrdinationEducational Leadership ProgramsFinancial Aid & ScholarshipsApplication DeadlinesTuition and Fees
Resources
Academic CalendarFaculty & Staff DirectoryRegister for CoursesRegistrarGann LibraryPodcastOn TorahCampus CafeSchoologyFacility RentalsEmployment OpportunitiesDirections & ParkingOnline StorePolicies, Accreditation & GuidesUpdate Your Information
Give
Give OnlineA Capital Campaign for Hebrew CollegeWays to GiveThe President’s CouncilAnnual Impact ReportBeit Midrash Day of Learning Sponsorships
Apply
Contact
Blog
Events
Donate
Search
Request Info
917-595-2100USA Number866-599-2534Israel Number
917-595-2100USA Number866-599-2534Israel Number
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.hebrewcollege.edu (the “Site”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
“Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit https://www.allaboutcookies.org.
“Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
“Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you register for a paid course/event or attempt to register for a paid course/event through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, if applicable, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our educational products or services. We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing,  advertising, and retargeting campaigns).
SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here.
We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at https://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by visiting these sites:
Facebook
Google
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: https://optout.aboutads.info/.
DO NOT TRACK
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
YOUR RIGHTS
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident, we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
DATA RETENTION
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
CHANGES
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
CONTACT US
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at webmaster@hebrewcollege.edu or by mail using the details provided below:
Hebrew Colege
160 Herrick Road
Newton Centre, MA 02459
United States
Updated October 2018
